<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Herald</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/</link><description>Recent content on Herald</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="bitcoin-herald.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Block #791985</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/posts/block-791985/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>bitcoin-herald.org/posts/block-791985/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://nostr.build/p/nb9820.png"/>
Hello, bitcoiner!
Today, 13 years ago, the first purchase of a physical product for bitcoin was made - Laszlo Heiniz exchanged 10,000 bitcoins for two pizzas. And while many today are perplexed as to how it was possible to spend such an incredible amount of bitcoins for lunch, the more interesting question is: how was it possible to part with two perfectly good pizzas in exchange for some magical internet money?</description></item><item><title>Block #791985</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/posts/block-792990/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>bitcoin-herald.org/posts/block-792990/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://nostr.build/p/nb10378.png"/>
Hey, bitcoiner!
Twelve years ago this week, the exchange rate of Bitcoin reached $10 for the very first time. Of course, Bitcoin took a nosedive afterward, convincing many that it was all over. People were panic-selling their magical internet money, and blaming Bitcoin for every possible sin. The only thing that&amp;rsquo;s changed after twelve years is the rate of bitcoin against dirty fiat; people are still buying bitcoin in an attempt to get rich quick, and if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t live up to their expectations of instant exponential growth, they complain about anything and everything, except their own greed.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>bitcoin-herald.org/about/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://nostr.build/p/nb9805.png"/>
Bitcoin Herald comes to you courtesy of a dynamic trio: two intrepid journalists tirelessly digging up the juiciest Bitcoin and Nostr news, plus a tech whiz making sure all the cogs are turning just right. We&amp;rsquo;re a modest team with big dreams, and we&amp;rsquo;re out to give news delivery a 180-degree spin.
Curious about the faces behind the Herald? Swing by our contacts page.
Loving our vibe? Help keep our mission alive by visiting the support page, or simply</description></item><item><title>Contacts</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/contacts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>bitcoin-herald.org/contacts/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://nostr.build/p/nb10425.png"/>
We&amp;rsquo;re majorly geeked up about Nostr, so the primo way to touch base with us is through a Nostr DM. But, for the old school among you, we&amp;rsquo;ve got email and some mainstream social media accounts, too. Now, don&amp;rsquo;t get it twisted. We&amp;rsquo;re not turning our backs on our fellow freedom fighters battling centralization and censorship. Nah, we&amp;rsquo;re just using those as bait to lure the normies into our purply, Bitcoin-enlightened world.</description></item><item><title>Support</title><link>bitcoin-herald.org/support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>bitcoin-herald.org/support/</guid><description>
&lt;img src="https://nostr.build/p/nb10428.png"/>
Lend a hand to our kick-ass cause - battling shitcoinery, championing censorship-resistant protocols, and restoring the glory days of true journalism.
Lightning: #</description></item></channel></rss>